Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Reports, 1952-2005; MC 00259 Series 10
  - Organizational Reports
    - NCSU School of Forestry Technical Reports
      - Technical Report 18: Collecting Pine Material in Mexico for Provenance Trials and Wood Studies, August, 1963; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Technical Report 20: Selected Methods and Materials for Finishing Appalachian Oak, January, 1964; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Technical Report 22: The Effects of Fertilization upon Wood Properties of Loblolly Pine (Pinus taeda L.), September, 1964; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Technical Report 26: Wood Yields from Loblolly Pine Stands of Different Age, Site, and Stand Density, September, 1965; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Technical Report 27: The Drying of Wood, September, 1965; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Technical Report 28: Growth, Form, and Disease Resistance in Four-Year-Old Control- and Five-Year-Old Open-Pollinated Progeny of Loblolly Pine Selected for Use in Seed Orchards, December, 1965; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Technical Report 29: Specific Gravity and Tracheid Length of Loblolly Pine in Maryland and Delaware, February, 1966; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Technical Report 30: An Annotated Bibliography of Hardwood Regeneration, undated; Formerly Box 61C (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Technical Report 34: An Annotated Bibliography of Hardwood Protection (Fire, Insects, Disease), undated; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Technical Report 37: An Annotated Bibliography of Hardwood Silvics, February, 1968; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Technical Report 38: Variation in Flowering and Its Effect on Seed Cost: A Study in Seed Orchards of Loblolly Pine, October, 1968; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Technical Report 39: Economics of Outdoor Recreation on Southern Commercial Timberlands: A Bibliography, November, 1969; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Technical Report 40: Inbreeding Depression in Metrical Traits of Loblolly Pine (Pinus Taeda L.) as a Result of Self-Pollination, December, 1969; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Technical Report 41: Variation and Inheritance of Stem Form and Bark Thickness in Young Loblolly Pine, January, 1970; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Technical Report 42: Characterization of the Strength of Juvenile Wood of Loblolly Pine (Pinus Taeda L.), December, 1969; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Technical Report 43: A Purchasing Decision Model with Application to Lumber Procurement in the Furniture Industry, February, 1970; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Technical Report 46: Tests on Grooved Lauan Plywood Panels and Proposed Allowable Stresses, June, 1971; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Technical Report 48: Response of Sycamore (Platanus Occidentalis L.) Families to Nitrogen Fertilization, October, 1972; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Technical Report 49: Decision Making Under Uncertainty: Should Hardwood Plantations be Established?, May, 1973; Formerly Box 61D (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Technical Report 50: Green Space for Air Pollution Control, July, 1973; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Technical Report 51: The Economics of Late Rotation Fertilization of Loblolly Pine Pulpwood Stands, March, 1974; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Technical Report 53: Forest Fertilization and Water Quality in the North Carolina Piedmont, undated; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Technical Report 55: Yields of Mixed Hardwood Stands Occurring Naturally on a Variety of Sites in the Southern United States, April, 1975; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Technical Report 56: The Effects from Rootraking on an Upland Piedmont Loblolly Pine (Pinus Taeda L.) Site, 1976; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Technical Report 57: A Recursive Spatial Equilibrium Model of the Softwood Timber Sector, March, 1978; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Technical Report 58: Effects of Fertilization on Susceptibility of Loblolly Pine to the Southern Pine Beetle, November, 1976; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Technical Report 59: Economically Optimum Spacing and Site Preparation for Slash Pine Plantations, July, 1977; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Technical Report 60: Site Preparation and Cultural Treatments Affect Growth of Planted Pinus Taeda L., January, 1978; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Technical Report 61: Maximum Likelihood Estimation for Selected Distributions (MLESD), 1978; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Technical Report 62: Potential of Black Alder in the South, 1980; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Technical Report 63: The Relationship of Soil, Foliar and Topographical Conditions to American Sycamore (Platanus Occidentalis L.) Growth in a Plantation, May 1980; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Technical Report 64: Loblolly Pine Tissue Culture: Present and Future Uses in Southern Forestry, March, 1981; Formerly Box 61E (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - North Carolina State University College of Natural Resources
      - Biennial Report, 2002-2004 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina State-Industry Cooperative Forest Tree Improvement Program
      - Third Annual Report, June, 1959; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Fourth Annual Report, June, 1960; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Fifth Annual Report, June, 1961; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Sixth Annual Report, June, 1962; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Seventh Annual Report, June, 1963; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Eighth Annual Report, June, 1964; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Ninth Annual Report, June, 1965; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Tenth Annual Report, June, 1966; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Eleventh Annual Report, June, 1967; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Twelfth Annual Report, May, 1968; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Thirteenth Annual Report, May, 1969; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Fourteenth Annual Report, May, 1970; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Fifteenth Annual Report, May, 1971; Formerly Box 61F (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Sixteenth Annual Report, May, 1972; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Seventeenth Annual Report, June, 1973; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Eighteenth Annual Report, June, 1974; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Nineteenth Annual Report, June, 1975; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Twentieth Annual Report, June, 1976; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Twenty-First Annual Report, May, 1977; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Twenty-Second Annual Report, June, 1978; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Twenty-Third Annual Report, June, 1979; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Twenty-Fourth Annual Report, June, 1980; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Twenty-Fifth Annual Report, June, 1981; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Twenty-Sixth Annual Report, June, 1982; Formerly Box 61G (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Twenty-Seventh Annual Report, June, 1983; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Twenty-Eighth Annual Report, June, 1984; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Twenty-Ninth Annual Report, June, 1985; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Thirty-Third Annual Report, May, 1989; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Thirty-Fourth Annual Report, May, 1990; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Thirty-Fifth Annual Report, May, 1991; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Thirty-Sixth Annual Report, May, 1992; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Thirty-Seventh Annual Report, May, 1993; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Thirty-Eighth Annual Report, 1994; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Thirty-Ninth Annual Report, 1995; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Fortieth Annual Report, 1996; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Forty-First Annual Report, 1997; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Forty-Second Annual Report, 1998; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Forty-Fourth Annual Report, 2000 (Box 382, Folder 2)
      - Forty-Seventh Annual Report, 2003 (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - Forty-Eighth Annual Report, 2004 (Box 382, Folder 4)
      - Forty-Ninth Annual Report, 2005 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - TAPPI
      - Quality Control in the Forest and in the Mill, 1974; Formerly Box 61H (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - AMBIO
      - Special Report Number 9, September 1998 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - AFOCEL
      - La Culture du Sapin de Douglas by De Champs, J., G. Touzet, and J.-Cl. Heinrich, 1978; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Culture de biomasse ligneuse: taillis a courte rotation, 1982; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - La Culture du Peuplier, by Barneoud, Cl. and P. Bonduelle, 1979; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Manuel de Populiculture, by Barneoud, C., P. Bonduelle, and J.M. Dubois, 1983; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations
      - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Tropical Forest Resources, 1982; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Tree Planting Practices in African Savannas, 1974; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Report on the FAO/DANIDA Training Course on Forest Tree Improvement Kenya, 1974; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Report on the Training Centre on Forest Tree Improvement (FAO) Rome, 1970 (Box 382, Folder 7)
      - Savanna Afforestation in Africa, 1977; Formerly Box 61J (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Forest Tree Improvement, 1985; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Genetic Resources of Tree Species in Arid and Semi-Arid Areas: A survey for the improvement of rural living in Latin America, Africa, India, and Southwest Asia, 1980; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Mejora Genetica de arboles forestales, 1980; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Reports - Canada
    - Pulp and Paper Research Institute of Canada, undated; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - First Draft of a Proposed Program of Woodlands Research for the Pulp and Paper Research Institute of Canada, by Lowell Besley, May 30, 1957; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Forest Nursery Station, Research Branch, Canada Department of Agriculture, Indian Head, Saskatchewan, 1961 Summary Report, 1962; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Forest Nursery Station, Research Branch, Canada Department of Agriculture, Indian Head, Saskatchewan 1963 Summary Report, 1964; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Forest Nursery Station, Research Branch, Canada Department of Agriculture, Indian Head, Saskatchewan 1966 Summary Report, 1967; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Forest Nursery Station, Research Branch, Canada Department of Agriculture, Indian Head, Saskatchewan 1967 Summary Report, 1968; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Poplar Breeding in Eastern Canada, by C. Heimburger, Ontario Department of Lands and Forests, Division of Research, 1958; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Forest Research Review 1956, British Columbia Forest Service, 1957; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Reports - Foreign Organizations
    - Agricultural Research Council of Central Africa Annual Report, July 1, 1965-June 30, 1966, Forest Genetics Research Team
    - Reports submitted by scientists-participants of the International Symposium on Forest Tree Breeding, Genetics and Seed Production of Coniferous Tree Species, Nobosibirsk, 1972; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Report on Forest Genetics and Forest Tree Improvement and Related Problems of Turkish Forestry, by Kani Isik, October, 1969; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Tree Breeding in Northern Rhodesia, by C.J.A. Shelbourne, Northern Rhodesia Government, 1962; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - The Jack Pine Genetics Program at Petawawa Forest Experiment Station, 1950-1970, by C.W. Yeatman, Canadian Forestry Service, 1974; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Savanna Forestry Research Station Annual Report, 1968-1969, Samaru, Zaria, Nigeria, undated; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Forest Tree Breeding in Japan, The Japanese Forest Tree Breeding Association, 1964; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Ruofsinkyla, The Experimental Areas of the Forest Research Institute of Finland, No. 2, undated; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Metsanjalostussaatio 1964, Foundation for Forest Tree Breeding in Finland, 1965; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Metsapuiden Rodunjalostussaation Toiminta 1959, Summary of Activity, 1960; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Metsapuiden Rodunjalostussaation Toiminta 1961, Summary of Activity, 1962; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Metsapuiden Rodunjalostussaation Toiminta 1962, Summary of Activity, 1963; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Commonwealth of Australia, Annual Report of the Forestry and Timber Bureau, December 21, 1952 (Box 382, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Reports - USA
    - A Progress Report, Loblolly Pine Seed Orchard, Tennessee River Pulp and Paper Company, October, 1961; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - American Chestnut Breeding Program at the University of Tennessee, by R.D. MacDonald, E. Thor, and J.O. Andes, 1962; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - A Report of Heteroplastic Grafting of Forest Trees--Including Results of Intergeneric and Interfamily Grafting, College of forestry at Syracuse University, 1964; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Annual Report of Project #768 - Genetic improvement of forest-tree planting stock, Wisconsin Conservation Department, undated; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Guide to Field Projects in Forest Tree Improvement at the Ohio Agricultural Experiment Station, undated; Formerly Box 61K (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Topical Reports
    - Brazil
      - Conifers Suitable for Planting in the State of Sao Paulo: Report to the Government of Brazil, Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1968; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Plano do Sistema de Unidades de Conservacao do Brasil. Ministerio da Agricultura, Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal, 1982; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Forestry Development and Research-Brazil: Research Needs in Silviculture and Forest Management, Technical Report 1, United Nations Development Programme, Food and Agriculture Organization, 1972; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Formacao, Manejo e Exploracao de Florestas com Especies de Rapido Crescimento, Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal, 1981; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - "Inventario Florestal Nacional: Florestas Nativas, Rio Grande do Sul," Ministerio da Agricultura, Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal, Departamento de Economia Florestal, 1983; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - "Inventario Florestal Nacional: Reflorestamento, Rio Grande do Sul," Ministerio da Agricultura, Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal, Departamento de Economia Florestal, 1983; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Forestry Development and Research Brazil: National Forest Policy Planning and Development, Technical Report 9, prepared for the Government of Brazil. Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1978; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - "Desenvolvimento e Pesquisa Florestal No Brasil: Necessidade de Pesquisa em Silvicultura e Manejo Florestal," by Maxwell R. Jacobs, Serie Tecnica, Projecto de Desenvolvimento e Pesquisa Florestal, 1973; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Central America
      - "The Pine Resources of Guatemala and Their Association with the Coniferous Forests of Mexico and Central America," by Carl M. Gallegos, January 1980 (Box 382, Folder 9)
    - Dendrology and Species
      - "Dasonomia mexicana: Origin and evolution of the genus Pinus (with special reference to Mexican pines)," by Piedra, T. Eguiluz, 1985; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - "Loblolly Pine Bibliography," by Keith W. Dorman and Ivan H. Sims, Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, November 1949; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - "Sitka Spruce: a bibliography with abstracts," Pacific Northwest Forest and Range Experiment Station, 1970; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - "Lodgepole Pine Bibliography," by David Tackle and D.I. Crossley, Intermountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, 1953; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - "Forest Trees of Texas: How to Know Them," Texas Forest Service, April 1963; Formerly Box 61L (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Thirteen Selected Articles from Lesnoe Khozyaistvo, Translated from Russian, U.S. Department of Commerce: Clearinghouse for Federal, Scientific and Technical Information, 1968; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - "Mountain Hemlock: A Bibliography with Abstracts," by Jerry F. Franklin, Pacific Northwest Forest and Range Experiment Station, October, 1962; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - "A Revised Shortleaf Pine Bibliography," by Glenn P. Haney, Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, December, 1962; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - "Shortleaf Pine Bibliography," by Glenn P. Haney, Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, January, 1955; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - "An annotated bibliography of western hemlock," by John Walters, The University of British Columbia, June, 1963; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - "Populus: A Bibliography of World Literature, 1854-1963," by R.E. Farmer, Jr. and J.S. McKnight, Southern Forest Experiment Station, 1967; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - "The Pines of Mexico," by George Russell Shaw, Publications of the Arnold Arboretum No. 1, J. R. Ruiter & Co., 1909; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - "Gross Characteristics of Lodgepole Pine Trees in North America," by Peter Koch, Intermountain Research Station, USDA Forest Service, 1987; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - "Utilization of Pinus Patula: An Annotated Bibliography," by J.A. Wright, Oxford Forestry Institute, Department of Plant Sciences, University of Oxford, 1994; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - "Ponderosa Pine Bibliography II, 1966-1970," by Elvera A. Axelton, Intermountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, 1974; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - "Ponderosa Pine Bibliography through 1965," by Elvera A. Axelton, Intermountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, 1967; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - "Growth and Site Relationships of Pinus caribaea Across the Caribbean Basin," by Leon H. Liegel, Southern Forest Experiment Station, 1991; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - "The Genus Pinus," by George Russell Shaw, Publications of the Arnold Arboretum No. 5., The Riverside Press, 1914; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - "Bibliography of Engelmann Spruce and Subalpine Fir," by Frank Ronco, Rocky Mountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, March, 1961; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - "Ordenacion de Nuestros Bosques de Coniferas: Regulacion de las Explotaciones y Determinacion de las Posibilidades Lenosas," by Mario Carrillo Garcia, Mexico: Editorial Cultura, 1955; Formerly Box 61M (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - "Bibliography of Pinus radiata," by A.P. Thomson, Forest Research Notes, July 1950; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - "Bibliography of Douglas-fir Provenance Studies, 1907-1974," compiled by Richard K. Hermann and Kim K. Ching, Forest Research Laboratory, School of Forestry, Oregon State University, July 1975; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - "An Annotated Bibliography of Cupressus Lusitanica," by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, undated; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - "Tree Planting Practices in Temperate Asia: Burma - India - Pakistan," by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1959; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - "Yellow Poplar Bibliography," compiled by Kingsley Taft Jr., August 28, 1959; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - "Ecology, Pathology, and Management of Port-Orford-Cedar (Chamaecyparis lawsoniana)," by Donald B. Zobel, Lewis F. Roth, and Glenn M. Hawk, Pacific Northwest Forest and Range Experiment Station, September, 1985; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - "Tropical Legumes: Resources for the Future," National Academy of Sciences, 1979; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - "La Variabilite genecologique du Hetre commun (Fagus silvatica L.) en Belgique," by A. Galoux, Ministere de l'Agriculture, Administration des Eaux et Forets, 1966; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - "Insights into the evolution of Picea inferred from chloroplast DNA," by Aoalsteinn Sigurgeirsson, Dissertation, Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, 1992; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - "Population Studies of Norway Spruce in Poland," Forest Research Institute in Warsaw, 1968; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - "Leucaena Research Reports," Department of Horticulture, University of Hawaii, July, 1981; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - "Cultural Treatment Effects on Growth of Four-Year Old loblolly Pine," North Carolina State Forest Fertilization Cooperative, School of Forest Resources, NCSU, June, 1985; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - "Ponderosa Pine Bibliography III: 1971 through 1975," Compiled by Elvera A. Axelton, Intermountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, March, 1977; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - "Longleaf Pine: An Annotated Bibliography, 1946 through 1967," by Thomas C. Croker, Jr., Southern Forest Experiment Station, 1968; Formerly Box 61N (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - "Annotated Bibliography of Walnut, Supplement No. 1," by Martha K. Dillow and Norman L. Hawker, North Central Forest Experiment Station, 1971; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - "Annotated Bibliography of Walnut, Supplement No. 2," by Martha K. Dillow, North Central Forest Experiment Station, 1975; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - "Forskningsverksamheten 1977," Department of Forest Genetics Research Notes, Royal College of Forestry, Stockholm, Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - "Effects of Thinning on Yield of Loblolly Pine in Central Louisiana," by Edward R. Andrulot, Lloyd P. Blackwell, and Paul Y. Burns, Division of Research, College of Life Sciences, Louisiana Tech University, 1972; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - "A Guide to Loblolly and Slash Pine Plantation Management in Southeastern USA," edited, with introductions by W.G. Wahlenberg, Georgia Forest Research Council, 1965; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - "Management Alternatives for Populus Tremuloides," by Jeanne Ferneyhough, April 7, 1985; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - "Aspen for High Quality Chemi-Mechanical Pulps: Overview for Alberta," prepared for Alberta Research Council by Woodbridge, Reed and Associates Ltd., February 24, 1981; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - "Guia: Dendrologica para Guatemala," by Julio Rodas Zamora, undated; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 8)